Welcome to OUSPG Open Gala!
We have gathered here today the trend setters of our society from movie, sound and software industry.
90 days, 6 projects.
It is quite a lot!
25+ organizations, 50+ people, 100+ encounters.
We used quite a lot of new tools.
Understatement of the week - "quite a lot".
We had both new tools, and new workflows.
All this while progressing the actual projects.
Over 2000 commits.
That is 22 commits per day!
My pet project, documenting and spinning with videos.
About 2700 views.
We've observed Github stars with 50hz frequency.
TryTLS took off around the time of shootouts.
We influenced the security of at least 3 programming language.
It is award-time!
We asked external judges to take a look at your projects...
- and to decide what's their favorite.
Tomi has influenced in Finland for long.
He's been running this T2 conference.
His choice was...
TryTLS!
I had fun - don't know about you!
Huge thanks to whole URL Handler team and all who participated.
Thanks for the summer! It has been educative and fun for me!
We should share this Mate with the whole team.
We've quickly learned new tools and workflows.
Which has been awesome! Thanks!